{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564733003","data":{"timestamp":" 947564733003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564733547","data":{"timestamp":" 947564733547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564735042","data":{"timestamp":" 947564735042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564735947","data":{"timestamp":" 947564735946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" ALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564736697","data":{"timestamp":" 947564736697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564737172","data":{"timestamp":" 947564737172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564737967","data":{"timestamp":" 947564737966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564739810","data":{"timestamp":" 947564739810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564746336","data":{"timestamp":" 947564746335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564752982","data":{"timestamp":" 947564752982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" START_MENGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564754032","data":{"timestamp":" 947564754032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" START_MAMANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564755640","data":{"timestamp":" 947564755640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564758075","data":{"timestamp":" 947564758075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564765388","data":{"timestamp":" 947564765388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564766324","data":{"timestamp":" 947564766324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564768836","data":{"timestamp":" 947564768836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564772497","data":{"timestamp":" 947564772497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564773831","data":{"timestamp":" 947564773831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564776160","data":{"timestamp":" 947564776160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564776373","data":{"timestamp":" 947564776373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564776847","data":{"timestamp":" 947564776847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564777750","data":{"timestamp":" 947564777750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564779506","data":{"timestamp":" 947564779506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TULIJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564780270","data":{"timestamp":" 947564780270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" LINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564780805","data":{"timestamp":" 947564780805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564782210","data":{"timestamp":" 947564782210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGETUGAWIA"," userResponse":" ANGETUGAWIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564783035","data":{"timestamp":" 947564783035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564783589","data":{"timestamp":" 947564783589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564788275","data":{"timestamp":" 947564788274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564789879","data":{"timestamp":" 947564789879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564791799","data":{"timestamp":" 947564791799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564793565","data":{"timestamp":" 947564793565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564795744","data":{"timestamp":" 947564795744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564797596","data":{"timestamp":" 947564797595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564799502","data":{"timestamp":" 947564799502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564801913","data":{"timestamp":" 947564801913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGETUGAWIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564803820","data":{"timestamp":" 947564803820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564805515","data":{"timestamp":" 947564805515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564808248","data":{"timestamp":" 947564808247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564809582","data":{"timestamp":" 947564809581"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKANGU"," userResponse":" KAKANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564810866","data":{"timestamp":" 947564810865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564812518","data":{"timestamp":" 947564812518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564815164","data":{"timestamp":" 947564815164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564816849","data":{"timestamp":" 947564816849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKANGU"," userResponse":" KAKANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564818257","data":{"timestamp":" 947564818257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564820776","data":{"timestamp":" 947564820776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564822977","data":{"timestamp":" 947564822977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYALA"," userResponse":" ALIYALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564823790","data":{"timestamp":" 947564823790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564824064","data":{"timestamp":" 947564824064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564825007","data":{"timestamp":" 947564825007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564826101","data":{"timestamp":" 947564826101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564826355","data":{"timestamp":" 947564826354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564830255","data":{"timestamp":" 947564830255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYALA"," userResponse":" START_BAADAYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564831477","data":{"timestamp":" 947564831477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYALA"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564833037","data":{"timestamp":" 947564833037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYALA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564833987","data":{"timestamp":" 947564833986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564835388","data":{"timestamp":" 947564835388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564837064","data":{"timestamp":" 947564837064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564838418","data":{"timestamp":" 947564838418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564841197","data":{"timestamp":" 947564841197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564843308","data":{"timestamp":" 947564843308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564847070","data":{"timestamp":" 947564847070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564849424","data":{"timestamp":" 947564849424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564851761","data":{"timestamp":" 947564851761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564851983","data":{"timestamp":" 947564851983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564853308","data":{"timestamp":" 947564853308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564853495","data":{"timestamp":" 947564853495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564854199","data":{"timestamp":" 947564854199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564854772","data":{"timestamp":" 947564854772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564855626","data":{"timestamp":" 947564855626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564855713","data":{"timestamp":" 947564855713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564857068","data":{"timestamp":" 947564857068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMELIWA"," userResponse":" YAMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564864754","data":{"timestamp":" 947564864754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564867091","data":{"timestamp":" 947564867091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564868750","data":{"timestamp":" 947564868750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564871385","data":{"timestamp":" 947564871384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564875800","data":{"timestamp":" 947564875800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564877699","data":{"timestamp":" 947564877698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564880019","data":{"timestamp":" 947564880019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564881636","data":{"timestamp":" 947564881636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564883844","data":{"timestamp":" 947564883844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564885970","data":{"timestamp":" 947564885970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMELIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564888903","data":{"timestamp":" 947564888903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULMWULIZA"," userResponse":" TULMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564889230","data":{"timestamp":" 947564889230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564889613","data":{"timestamp":" 947564889612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564890412","data":{"timestamp":" 947564890412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," userResponse":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564891055","data":{"timestamp":" 947564891055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564895857","data":{"timestamp":" 947564895856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TULMWULIZA"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564897944","data":{"timestamp":" 947564897944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULMWULIZA"," userResponse":" TULMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564898169","data":{"timestamp":" 947564898169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564901372","data":{"timestamp":" 947564901371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564909321","data":{"timestamp":" 947564909321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564909995","data":{"timestamp":" 947564909995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564912765","data":{"timestamp":" 947564912764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564913624","data":{"timestamp":" 947564913623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564914795","data":{"timestamp":" 947564914795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564916256","data":{"timestamp":" 947564916255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564917087","data":{"timestamp":" 947564917086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564919028","data":{"timestamp":" 947564919027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," userResponse":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564921466","data":{"timestamp":" 947564921466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564924773","data":{"timestamp":" 947564924773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564934334","data":{"timestamp":" 947564934334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564936269","data":{"timestamp":" 947564936269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564938440","data":{"timestamp":" 947564938440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564941118","data":{"timestamp":" 947564941118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564943641","data":{"timestamp":" 947564943641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564944934","data":{"timestamp":" 947564944934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564946028","data":{"timestamp":" 947564946028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" KUTULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564947310","data":{"timestamp":" 947564947309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564948069","data":{"timestamp":" 947564948068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564950646","data":{"timestamp":" 947564950646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564953404","data":{"timestamp":" 947564953404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564955054","data":{"timestamp":" 947564955054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564957069","data":{"timestamp":" 947564957069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564959148","data":{"timestamp":" 947564959147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564961535","data":{"timestamp":" 947564961534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564963103","data":{"timestamp":" 947564963103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564964020","data":{"timestamp":" 947564964019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564964285","data":{"timestamp":" 947564964284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564965137","data":{"timestamp":" 947564965136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564965271","data":{"timestamp":" 947564965271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564965972","data":{"timestamp":" 947564965971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564967494","data":{"timestamp":" 947564967493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAUMWA"," userResponse":" NAUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564967824","data":{"timestamp":" 947564967823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564968546","data":{"timestamp":" 947564968545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564971617","data":{"timestamp":" 947564971617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564974197","data":{"timestamp":" 947564974196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564976441","data":{"timestamp":" 947564976441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564978107","data":{"timestamp":" 947564978107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564980334","data":{"timestamp":" 947564980333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564981977","data":{"timestamp":" 947564981977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564983657","data":{"timestamp":" 947564983656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564985557","data":{"timestamp":" 947564985557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAUMWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564987361","data":{"timestamp":" 947564987361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564989323","data":{"timestamp":" 947564989323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564991951","data":{"timestamp":" 947564991950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564992862","data":{"timestamp":" 947564992862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TULIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564993556","data":{"timestamp":" 947564993555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564994583","data":{"timestamp":" 947564994583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564995395","data":{"timestamp":" 947564995394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564996165","data":{"timestamp":" 947564996164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564997097","data":{"timestamp":" 947564997096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564998222","data":{"timestamp":" 947564998221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564998693","data":{"timestamp":" 947564998691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947564999549","data":{"timestamp":" 947564999548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565000905","data":{"timestamp":" 947565000905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGECHAPWA"," userResponse":" ANGECHAPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565001116","data":{"timestamp":" 947565001115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565001624","data":{"timestamp":" 947565001624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565005547","data":{"timestamp":" 947565005547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565007516","data":{"timestamp":" 947565007515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565009370","data":{"timestamp":" 947565009370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565011333","data":{"timestamp":" 947565011333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565014730","data":{"timestamp":" 947565014730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565016796","data":{"timestamp":" 947565016795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565018589","data":{"timestamp":" 947565018589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565021217","data":{"timestamp":" 947565021217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565023016","data":{"timestamp":" 947565023016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565024930","data":{"timestamp":" 947565024930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565027090","data":{"timestamp":" 947565027089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGECHAPWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565029057","data":{"timestamp":" 947565029056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565030946","data":{"timestamp":" 947565030945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565033807","data":{"timestamp":" 947565033806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565035170","data":{"timestamp":" 947565035170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPOPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565035847","data":{"timestamp":" 947565035846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFUU"," userResponse":" NAFUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565037436","data":{"timestamp":" 947565037436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565038736","data":{"timestamp":" 947565038735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUOMBA"," userResponse":" ALITUOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565039973","data":{"timestamp":" 947565039973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565044125","data":{"timestamp":" 947565044125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565046552","data":{"timestamp":" 947565046552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565048481","data":{"timestamp":" 947565048481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565050401","data":{"timestamp":" 947565050401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565052607","data":{"timestamp":" 947565052607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUOMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565054880","data":{"timestamp":" 947565054880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565056906","data":{"timestamp":" 947565056905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565057162","data":{"timestamp":" 947565057161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565071040","data":{"timestamp":" 947565071040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565085368","data":{"timestamp":" 947565085368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" e1aa254e-2516-4ed1-9cc3-ce3b70f5229f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565106889","data":{"timestamp":" 947565106889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 0d027618-3f1f-4930-acd5-4b26708d06a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_chao-haha-mito"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565112152","data":{"timestamp":" 947565112152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 0d027618-3f1f-4930-acd5-4b26708d06a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fugo_lake-dogo-fugo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fugo"," userResponse":" fugo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565118611","data":{"timestamp":" 947565118611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 0d027618-3f1f-4930-acd5-4b26708d06a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kitu_vuta-nije-kitu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kitu"," userResponse":" kitu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565125089","data":{"timestamp":" 947565125089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 0d027618-3f1f-4930-acd5-4b26708d06a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_maua_maua-giza-dogo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maua"," userResponse":" maua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565137588","data":{"timestamp":" 947565137588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 0d027618-3f1f-4930-acd5-4b26708d06a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nalo_pili-lisa-nalo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nalo"," userResponse":" nalo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565145463","data":{"timestamp":" 947565145463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 0d027618-3f1f-4930-acd5-4b26708d06a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huyo_huyo-kufa-nini"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huyo"," userResponse":" huyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565152854","data":{"timestamp":" 947565152854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 0d027618-3f1f-4930-acd5-4b26708d06a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndio_nane-ndio-kila"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndio"," userResponse":" nane"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565159204","data":{"timestamp":" 947565159204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 0d027618-3f1f-4930-acd5-4b26708d06a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndio_nane-ndio-kila"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndio"," userResponse":" ndio"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565165358","data":{"timestamp":" 947565165358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 0d027618-3f1f-4930-acd5-4b26708d06a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_damu_tuna-damu-siku"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" damu"," userResponse":" damu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565172535","data":{"timestamp":" 947565172535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 0d027618-3f1f-4930-acd5-4b26708d06a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naye"," userResponse":" naye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565177199","data":{"timestamp":" 947565177199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 0d027618-3f1f-4930-acd5-4b26708d06a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_saba-kuyu-sisi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" saba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565182518","data":{"timestamp":" 947565182518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 0d027618-3f1f-4930-acd5-4b26708d06a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_saba-kuyu-sisi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565188277","data":{"timestamp":" 947565188277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 0d027618-3f1f-4930-acd5-4b26708d06a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_saba-kuyu-sisi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565215075","data":{"timestamp":" 947565215075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_limeke__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565227198","data":{"timestamp":" 947565227198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_limeke__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565234635","data":{"timestamp":" 947565234635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_limeke__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565240267","data":{"timestamp":" 947565240267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_limeke__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565250008","data":{"timestamp":" 947565250008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_limeke__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565259272","data":{"timestamp":" 947565259271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_limeke__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565272106","data":{"timestamp":" 947565272106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_limeke__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565294442","data":{"timestamp":" 947565294442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ikavu___"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565301485","data":{"timestamp":" 947565301484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ikavu___"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565309177","data":{"timestamp":" 947565309177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ikavu___"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565316720","data":{"timestamp":" 947565316720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ikavu___"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565325049","data":{"timestamp":" 947565325049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ikavu___"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565334185","data":{"timestamp":" 947565334185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ikavu___"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565345976","data":{"timestamp":" 947565345976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ikavu___"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565359120","data":{"timestamp":" 947565359120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ikavu___"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565363806","data":{"timestamp":" 947565363806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ikavu___"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565376740","data":{"timestamp":" 947565376740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nje__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565383830","data":{"timestamp":" 947565383830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nje__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565392692","data":{"timestamp":" 947565392692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nje__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565399218","data":{"timestamp":" 947565399218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nje__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565406591","data":{"timestamp":" 947565406591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nje__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565415453","data":{"timestamp":" 947565415453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nje__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565427657","data":{"timestamp":" 947565427657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_dema__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565433244","data":{"timestamp":" 947565433244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_dema__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565444386","data":{"timestamp":" 947565444386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_dema__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565452499","data":{"timestamp":" 947565452499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_dema__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565462249","data":{"timestamp":" 947565462248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ba__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565470904","data":{"timestamp":" 947565470904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ba__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565480235","data":{"timestamp":" 947565480235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ba__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565488009","data":{"timestamp":" 947565488009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ba__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565496084","data":{"timestamp":" 947565496083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ba__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" x"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565508444","data":{"timestamp":" 947565508443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ba__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565525598","data":{"timestamp":" 947565525597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kukusanyi__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565582486","data":{"timestamp":" 947565582486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kukusanyi__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" q"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565596188","data":{"timestamp":" 947565596187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kukusanyi__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565615922","data":{"timestamp":" 947565615922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kukusanyi__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565628776","data":{"timestamp":" 947565628776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kukusanyi__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565633902","data":{"timestamp":" 947565633901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kukusanyi__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565642864","data":{"timestamp":" 947565642864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mji__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565649662","data":{"timestamp":" 947565649662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mji__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565658794","data":{"timestamp":" 947565658794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mji__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565667631","data":{"timestamp":" 947565667631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mji__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565682044","data":{"timestamp":" 947565682044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mji__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565697045","data":{"timestamp":" 947565697045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alija__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565709362","data":{"timestamp":" 947565709362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alija__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565719724","data":{"timestamp":" 947565719723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alija__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565725869","data":{"timestamp":" 947565725869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alija__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565748687","data":{"timestamp":" 947565748686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mia__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565757679","data":{"timestamp":" 947565757679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mia__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565765907","data":{"timestamp":" 947565765907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mia__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565773313","data":{"timestamp":" 947565773313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mia__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565780395","data":{"timestamp":" 947565780395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mia__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565786624","data":{"timestamp":" 947565786624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mia__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565794110","data":{"timestamp":" 947565794110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mia__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565807690","data":{"timestamp":" 947565807690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565817052","data":{"timestamp":" 947565817052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565826357","data":{"timestamp":" 947565826357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565832170","data":{"timestamp":" 947565832170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565839127","data":{"timestamp":" 947565839127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565847420","data":{"timestamp":" 947565847419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565852699","data":{"timestamp":" 947565852699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565858620","data":{"timestamp":" 947565858620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565875516","data":{"timestamp":" 947565875516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" a6638989-4210-4c9a-b867-7919c6490667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565895953","data":{"timestamp":" 947565895953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_damu_tuna-damu-siku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" damu"," userResponse":" damu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565902318","data":{"timestamp":" 947565902318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fugo_lake-dogo-fugo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fugo"," userResponse":" fugo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565911949","data":{"timestamp":" 947565911949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naye"," userResponse":" hili"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565918366","data":{"timestamp":" 947565918366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naye"," userResponse":" hili"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565926239","data":{"timestamp":" 947565926238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naye"," userResponse":" wana"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565935815","data":{"timestamp":" 947565935815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_chao-haha-mito"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565943714","data":{"timestamp":" 947565943714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kitu_vuta-nije-kitu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kitu"," userResponse":" kitu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565948920","data":{"timestamp":" 947565948920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_saba-kuyu-sisi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565953631","data":{"timestamp":" 947565953631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_maua_maua-giza-dogo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maua"," userResponse":" maua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565958131","data":{"timestamp":" 947565958131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nalo_pili-lisa-nalo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nalo"," userResponse":" pili"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565963795","data":{"timestamp":" 947565963795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nalo_pili-lisa-nalo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nalo"," userResponse":" nalo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565970910","data":{"timestamp":" 947565970910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huyo_huyo-kufa-nini"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huyo"," userResponse":" huyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565978222","data":{"timestamp":" 947565978222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndio_nane-ndio-kila"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndio"," userResponse":" ndio"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565984016","data":{"timestamp":" 947565984014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" 3ada53cd-e6b7-48e9-a514-1e4d96ebdd6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ndio_nane-ndio-kila"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947565998329","data":{"timestamp":" 947565998329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" c41e5755-4769-4b73-8d7f-823d359ea8fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_chao-haha-mito"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566001777","data":{"timestamp":" 947566001777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_072514"," gameId":" c41e5755-4769-4b73-8d7f-823d359ea8fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_chao-haha-mito"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}